I don't even know what the f*** to say anymore.
I really don't.
The levels of hatred, racism, bigotry, arrogance, ignorance, and human wickedness
I've seen over the past few weeks are f***ing staggering.
It's mind-boggling that this is 2023.
I'm ashamed to even be breathing some of the f***ing same air as you f***ing scumbags.
Somebody asked me the other day if I think a revolution is coming.
We're in one f***ing now.
The whole world is at war f***ing now.
And it is a war to save the soul of f***ing humanity.
And everybody needs to pick a f***ing side because we are fighting pure f***ing evil.
We are in a media war.
We are in a spiritual war.
We are in a war for the soul of humanity.
And we are in a war against power structure.
And everybody is going to get bloody on this.
I s*** you the f***ing not.
All you people hiding behind your keyboards and hiding behind your businesses and hiding
because you're somebody important.
Everybody is going to get touched on this one.
Nobody is going to forget that you were a coward.
Nobody.